A Guide to the Virginia Auditor of Public Accounts - Tobacco and Flour Inspector Records, 1776-1878
Library of Virginia
- Series IX: Public Tobacco Warehouse vouchers, 1776-1865 (APA 293)., Extent: XX cubic feet. (Box XX-XX)
  - Vouchers (Amherst Warehouse), 1814 Jan 10. (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Vouchers (Johnson's Warehouse), 1814 Jan 13. (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Vouchers (Amherst Warehouse), 1814 Feb 3. (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Vouchers (Trent's Warehouse), 1814 Mar 21. (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Vouchers (Prince George/Petersburs Warehouses), 1814 June 22. (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Vouchers (Rockett's Warehouse), 1814 July 5. (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Vouchers (Rockett's Warehouse), 1814 July 9. (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Vouchers (Rockett's Warehouse), 1814 Aug 11. (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Vouchers (Petersburg Warehouses), 1814 Aug 22. (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Vouchers (Petersburg Warehouses), 1814 Aug 22. (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Vouchers (Johnson's Warehouse), 1814 Oct 11. (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Vouchers (Rockett's Warehouse), 1814 Oct 13. (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Vouchers (James River Canal Warehouse), 1814 Oct 15. (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Vouchers (Bethel and Madison Warehouses), 1814 Oct 22. (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Vouchers (Amherst Warehouse), 1814 Oct 25. (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Vouchers (Cannon's Warehouse), 1814 Oct 25. (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Vouchers (Horsley's Warehouse), 1814 Oct 25. (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Vouchers (Petersburg Warehouses), 1814 Oct 27. (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Vouchers (Petersburg Warehouses), 1814 Oct 29. (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Vouchers (Petersburg Warehouses), 1814 Nov 8. (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - Vouchers (Davis' Warehouse), 1814 Nov 15. (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - Vouchers (Bollingbrook Warehouse), 1814 Dec 8. (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - Vouchers (Lynchburg Warehouses), 1814 Dec 20. (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - Vouchers (Blandford's Warehouse), 1814 Dec 28. (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - Vouchers (Boyd's Warehouse), 1814 Dec 28. (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - Vouchers (Seabrook's Warehouse), 1815 Jan 18. (Box 11, Folder 41)
  - Vouchers (Moore's Warehouse), 1815 Feb 3. (Box 11, Folder 42)
  - Vouchers (Johnson's, Trent's, and Manchester Warehouses), 1815 Feb 16. (Box 11, Folder 43)
  - Vouchers (Amherst Warehouse), 1815 July 24. (Box 11, Folder 44)
  - Vouchers (Petersburg Warehouses), 1815 Sept 30. (Box 11, Folder 45)
  - Vouchers (Richmond Warehouses), 1815 Oct 6. (Box 11, Folder 46)
  - Vouchers (Cannons' Warehouse), 1815 Oct 27. (Box 11, Folder 47)
  - Vouchers (Chesterfield County Warehouses), 1815 Dec 14. (Box 11, Folder 48)
  - Vouchers (Lynchburg Warehouses), 1815 Dec 19. (Box 11, Folder 49)
  - Vouchers (Petersburg Warehouses), 1816 Jan 8. (Box 11, Folder 50)
  - Vouchers (Trent's Warehouse), 1816 Jan 11. (Box 11, Folder 51)
  - Vouchers (Johnson's Warehouse), 1816 Feb 29. (Box 11, Folder 52)
  - Vouchers (Richmond Warehouses), 1816 Apr 12. (Box 11, Folder 53)
  - Vouchers (Petersburg Warehouses), 1816 June 14. (Box 11, Folder 54)
  - Vouchers (Lynchburg Warehouses), 1816 Oct 23. (Box 11, Folder 55)
  - Vouchers (Seabrook's and Shockoe Warehouses), 1816 Nov 11. (Box 11, Folder 56)
  - Vouchers (Boxwell's Warehouse), 1817 Jan 2. (Box 11, Folder 57)
  - Vouchers (Cross Street Warehouse), 1817 Jan 7. (Box 11, Folder 58)
  - Vouchers (High Street Warehouse), 1817 Jan 7. (Box 11, Folder 58)
  - Vouchers (Petersburg Warehouses), 1817 June 14. (Box 11, Folder 59)
  - Vouchers (Cannon's Warehouse), 1817 Oct 30. (Box 11, Folder 60)
  - Vouchers (Falmouth and Fredericksburg Warehouses), 1817 Oct 30. (Box 11, Folder 60)
  - Vouchers (Johnson's and Manchester Warehouses), 1817 Nov 14. (Box 11, Folder 61)
  - Vouchers (Lynchburg Warehouses), 1817 Nov 22. (Box 11, Folder 62)
  - Vouchers (Seabrook and Shockoe Warehouses), 1817 Dec 3. (Box 11, Folder 63)
  - Vouchers (Richmond Warehouses), 1817 Dec 16. (Box 11, Folder 64)
  - Vouchers (Coan's Warehouse), 1817 Dec 20. (Box 11, Folder 65)
  - Vouchers (Davis Warehouse), 1817 Dec 26. (Box 11, Folder 66)
  - Vouchers (Tye River Warehouse), 1818 Jan 6. (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Vouchers (Richmond Warehouses), 1818 Feb 11. (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Vouchers (Royster's Warehouse), 1818 Apr 30. (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Vouchers (Royster's Warehouse), 1818 June 15. (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Vouchers (Haskington Warehouse), 1818 July 23. (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Vouchers (Royster's Warehouse), 1818 Sept 28. (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Vouchers (Richmond and Manchester Warehouses), 1818 Nov 9. (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Vouchers (Cannon's Warehouse), 1818 Nov 27. (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Vouchers (Shockoe Warehouse), 1818 Dec 9. (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Vouchers (Johnson's, Trent's and Manchester Warehouses), 1818 Dec 22. (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Vouchers (Haskington Warehouse), 1818 Dec. (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Vouchers (Abbeyville Warehouse), 1819 Jan 6. (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Vouchers (Lynchburg Warehouses), 1819 Jan 16. (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Vouchers (Petersburg Warehouses), 1819 Feb 3. (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Vouchers (Shockoe Warehouse), 1819 Feb 3. (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Vouchers (Fredericksburg Warehouse), 1819 Feb 5. (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Vouchers (Liberty Warehouse), 1819 Feb 16. (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Vouchers (Lynchburg Warehouses), 1819 Feb 26. (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Vouchers (Johnson's, Trent's, and Manchster Warehouses), 1819 May 5. (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Vouchers (Petersburg Warehouses), 1819 Aug 2. (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Vouchers (Pannell's Warehouse), 1819 Oct 13. (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Vouchers (Seabrook's Warehouse), 1819Oct 23. (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Vouchers (Claiburne's Warehouse), 1819 Nov 2. (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Vouchers (Falmouth and Fredericksburg Warehouses), 1819 Nov 5. (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Vouchers (Wicomico Warehouse), 1819 Nov 20. (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Vouchers (Royster's Warehouse), 1819 Dec 2. (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Vouchers (Cannon's Warehouse), 1819 Dec 16. (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Vouchers (Lynchburg Warehouses), 1820 Jan 8. (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Vouchers (Johnson's Warehouse), 1820 Jan 14. (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Vouchers (Trent's Warehouse), 1820 Jan 14. (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Vouchers (Pannell's Warehouse), 1820 Feb 12. (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Vouchers (Wimbish's Warehouse), 1820 Mar 14. (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Vouchers (Johnson's, Trent's, and Manchester Warehouses), 1820 Apr 15. (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Vouchers (Cannon's Warehouse), 1820 May 16. (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Vouchers (Horsley's Warehouse), 1820 June 1. (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Vouchers (Westbrook Warehouse), 1820 June 23. (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - Vouchers (Johnson's, Trent's, and Manchster Warehouses), 1820 July 3. (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - Vouchers (Trent's Warehouse), 1820 Aug 30. (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - Vouchers (Cannon's Warehouse), 1820 Oct 5. (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - Vouchers (Falmouth and Fredericksburg Warehouses), 1820 Oct 24. (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - Vouchers (Horsley's Warehouse), 1820 Oct 31. (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - Vouchers (Falmouth and Fredericksburg Warehouses), 1820 Nov 11. (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - Vouchers (Lynchburg Warehouses), 1820 Nov 20. (Box 12, Folder 41)
  - Vouchers (Anderson's Warehouse), 1820 Dec 14. (Box 12, Folder 42)
  - Vouchers (Brookneal Warehouse), 1820 Dec 20. (Box 12, Folder 43)
  - Vouchers (Seabrook's and Shockoe Warehouses), 1821 Jan 3. (Box 12, Folder 44)
  - Vouchers (Johnson's, Trent's and Manchester Warehouses), 1821 Feb 24. (Box 12, Folder 45)
  - Vouchers (Randolph's Warehouse), 1821 Mar 23. (Box 12, Folder 46)
  - Vouchers (Johnson's Warehouse), 1821 Mar 28. (Box 12, Folder 47)
  - Vouchers (Seabrook's and Shockoe Warehouses), 1821 Apr 12. (Box 12, Folder 48)
  - Vouchers (Farmville Warehouse), 1821 Apr 21. (Box 12, Folder 49)
  - Vouchers (Trent's Warehouse), 1821 May 19. (Box 12, Folder 50)
  - Vouchers (Cannon's Warehouse), 1821 May 26. (Box 12, Folder 51)
  - Vouchers (Johnson's, Trent's and Manchester Warehouses), 1821 May 28. (Box 12, Folder 52)
  - Vouchers (Seabrook's and Shockoe Warehouses), 1821 Aug 24. (Box 12, Folder 53)
  - Vouchers (Seabrook's and Shockoe Warehouses), 1821 Aug 31. (Box 12, Folder 54)
  - Vouchers (Richmond and Manchster Warehouses), 1821 Sept 19. (Box 12, Folder 55)
  - Vouchers (Richmond and Manchester Warehouses), 1821 Oct 13. (Box 12, Folder 56)
  - Vouchers (Johnson's and Trent's Warehouses), 1821 Oct 16. (Box 12, Folder 57)
  - Vouchers (Johnson's Warehouse), 1821 Oct 20. (Box 12, Folder 58)
  - Vouchers (Johnson's Warehouse), 1821 Oct 23. (Box 12, Folder 59)
  - Vouchers (Falmouth and Fredericksburg Warehouses), 1821 Nov 2. (Box 12, Folder 60)
  - Vouchers (Lynchburg Warehouses), 1821 Dec 22. (Box 12, Folder 61)
  - Vouchers (Richmond and Manchester Warehouses), 1822 Jan 8. (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Vouchers (Petersburg Warehouses), 1822 jan 22. (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Vouchers (Friend's Warehouse), 1822 Jan 26. (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Vouchers (Seabrook's Warehouse), 1822 Jan 26. (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Vouchers (Falmouth and Fredericksburg Warehouses), 1822 Feb 6. (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Vouchers (Seabrook's Warehouse), 1822 Feb 7. (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Vouchers (Richmond and Manchester Warehouses), 1822 Apr 3. (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Vouchers (Richmond and Manchester Warehouses), 1822 May 27. (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Vouchers (Petersburg Warehouses), 1822 June 3. (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Vouchers (Richmond and Manchester Warehouses), 1822 July 2. (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Vouchers (Richmond and Manchester Warehouses), 1822 July 18. (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Vouchers (Seabrook's and Shockoe Warehouses), 1822 Sept 12. (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Vouchers (Falmouth and Fredericksburg Warehouses), 1822 Oct 7. (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Vouchers (Richmond and Manchester Warehouses), 1822 Oct 9. (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Vouchers (Horsley's Warehouse), 1822 Oct 31. (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Vouchers (Fredericksburg Warehouses), 1822 Nov 1. (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Vouchers (Richmond and Manchester Warehouses), 1822 Nov 2. (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Vouchers (Shockoe Warehouse), 1822 Dec 3. (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Vouchers (Lynchburg Warehouses), 1822 Dec 7. (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Vouchers (Richmond and Manchester Warehouses), 1823 Jan 7. (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Vouchers (Falmouth and Fredericksburg Warehouses), 1823 Jan 17. (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Vouchers (Richmond and Manchester Warehouses), 1823 Feb 6. (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Vouchers (Richmond and Manchester Warehouses), 1823 Apr 9. (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Vouchers (Petersburg Warehouses), 1823 Apr 29. (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Vouchers (Trent's Warehouse), 1823 May 16. (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Vouchers (Richmond and Manchester Warehouses), 1823 June 5. (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Vouchers (Botetourt County (Union) Warehouse), 1823 June 23. (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Vouchers (Richmond and Manchester Warehouses), 1823 July 9. (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Vouchers (Cannon's Warehouse), 1823 July 24. (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Vouchers (Richmond and Manchester Warehouses), 1823 Aug 4. (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Vouchers (Richmond Warehouses), 1823 Aug 7. (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Vouchers (Manchester Warehouse), 1823 Aug 9. (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Vouchers (Richmond and Manchester Warehouses), 1823 Oct 8. (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - Vouchers (Horsley's Warehouse), 1823 Oct 29. (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - Vouchers (Cannon's Warehouse), 1823 Oct 30. (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - Vouchers (Richmond and Manchester Warehouses), 1823 Nov 5. (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - Vouchers (Lynchburg Warehouses), 1823 Dec 1. (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - Vouchers (Richmond and Manchester Warehouses), 1824 Jan 6. (Box 13, Folder 37)
  - Vouchers (Richmond and Manchester Warehouses), 1824 Jan 21. (Box 13, Folder 38)
  - Vouchers (Johnson's and Manchester Warehouses), 1824 Feb 5. (Box 13, Folder 39)
  - Vouchers (Richmond and Manchester Warehouses), 1824 Apr 7. (Box 13, Folder 40)
  - Vouchers (Petersburg Warehouse), 1824 June 30. (Box 13, Folder 41)
  - Vouchers (Richmond and Manchester Warehouses), 1824 July 1. (Box 13, Folder 42)
  - Vouchers (Richmond and Manchester Warehouses), 1824 July 7. (Box 13, Folder 43)
  - Vouchers (Richmond and Manchester Warehouses), 1824 Aug 10. (Box 13, Folder 44)
  - Vouchers (Johnson's and Manchester Warehouses), 1824 Aug 12. (Box 13, Folder 45)
  - Vouchers (Fredericksburg Warehouse), 1824 Oct 15. (Box 13, Folder 46)
  - Vouchers (Richmond and Manchester Warehouses), 1824 Oct 15. (Box 13, Folder 46)
  - Vouchers (Richmond and Manchester Warehouses), 1824. (Box 13, Folder 47)
  - Vouchers (Lynchburg Warehouses), 1824 Dec 27. (Box 13, Folder 48)
  - Vouchers (Richmond and Manchester Warehouses), 1825 Jan 4. (Box 13, Folder 49)
  - Vouchers (Johnson's Warehouse), 1825 Jan 28. (Box 13, Folder 50)
  - Vouchers (Richmond and Manchester Warehouses), 1825 Feb 5. (Box 13, Folder 51)
  - Vouchers (Richmond and Manchester Warehouses), 1825 Apr 9. (Box 13, Folder 52)
  - Vouchers (Richmond and Manchester Warehouses), 1825 Apr 29. (Box 13, Folder 53)
  - Vouchers (Richmond and Manchester Warehouses), 1825 Aug 13. (Box 13, Folder 54)
  - Vouchers (Richmond and Manchester Warehouses), 1825 Oct 5. (Box 13, Folder 55)
  - Vouchers (Lynchburg Warehouses), 1825 Oct 31. (Box 13, Folder 56)
  - Vouchers (Fredericksburg Warehouse), 1825 Nov 1. (Box 13, Folder 57)
  - Vouchers (Richmond and Manchester Warehouses), 1825 Dec 10. (Box 13, Folder 58)
  - Vouchers (Richmond and Manchester Warehouses), 1826 Jan 5. (Box 13, Folder 59)
  - Vouchers (Richmond and Manchester Warehouses), 1826 Apt 6. (Box 13, Folder 60)
  - Vouchers (Richmond and Manchester Warehouses), 1826 Apr 14. (Box 13, Folder 61)
  - Vouchers (Richmond and Manchester Warehouses), 1826 May 27. (Box 13, Folder 62)
  - Vouchers (Richmond and Manchester Warehouses), 1826 July 5. (Box 13, Folder 63)
  - Vouchers (Richmond and Manchester Warehouses), 1826 July 24. (Box 13, Folder 64)
  - Vouchers (Petersburg Warehouses), 1826 Aug 19. (Box 13, Folder 65)
  - Vouchers (Richmond and Manchester Warehouses), 1826 Oct 5. (Box 13, Folder 66)
  - Vouchers (Lynchburg Warehouses), 1826 Oct 9. (Box 13, Folder 67)
  - Vouchers (Richmond and Manchester Warehouses), 1826 Oct 17. (Box 13, Folder 68)
  - Vouchers (Johnson's and Manchester Warehouses), 1826 Oct 18. (Box 13, Folder 69)
  - Vouchers (James River Canal Warehouse), 1826 Oct 26. (Box 13, Folder 70)
  - Vouchers (Fredericksburg Warehouse), 1826 Nov 2. (Box 13, Folder 71)
  - Vouchers (Richmond and Manchester Warehouses), 1826 Jan 2. (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Vouchers (Richmond and Manchester Warehouses), 1826 Feb 23. (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Vouchers (Richmond and Manchester Warehouses), 1826 Apr 4. (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Vouchers (Liberty and Lynch's Warehouses), 1826 May 4. (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Vouchers (Richmond and Manchester Warehouses), 1826 May 10. (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Vouchers (Richmond and Manchester Warehouses), 1826 July 5. (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Vouchers (Richmond and Manchester Warehouses), 1826 July 13. (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Vouchers (Johnson's and Manchester Warehouses), 1826 Aug 28. (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Vouchers (Richmond and Manchester Warehouses), 1826 Oct 3. (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Vouchers (Lynchburg Warehouses), 1827 Feb 23. (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Vouchers (Lynchburg Warehouses), 1827 Oct 27. (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Vouchers (Fredericksburg Warehouses), 1827 Nov 1. (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Vouchers (Lynchburg Warehouses), 1827 Dec 3. (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Vouchers (Richmond and Manchester Warehouses), 1827 Dec 6. (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Vouchers (Johnson's and Manchester Warehouses), 1827 Dec 15. (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Vouchers (Buckingham County Warehouses), 1828 Jan 23. (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Vouchers (Richmond and Manchester Warehouses), 1828 Mar 14. (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Vouchers (Richmond and Manchester Warehouses), 1828 May 19. (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Vouchers (Richmond and Manchester Warehouses), 1828 Mar 22. (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Vouchers (Richmond and Manchester Warehouses), 1828 May 20. (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Vouchers (Richmond and Manchester Warehouses), 1828 July 10. (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Vouchers (Richmond and Manchester Warehouses), 1828 July 29. (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Vouchers (Richmond and Manchester Warehouses), 1828 Sept 4. (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Vouchers (Richmond and Manchester Warehouses), 1828 Sept 24. (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Vouchers (Lynchburg Warehouses), 1828 Oct 17. (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Vouchers (Superintendent of Public Warehouses), 1828 Oct 22. (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Vouchers (Richmond and Manchester Warehouses), 1829 Nov 28. (Box 14, Folder 26a)
  - Vouchers (Richmond and Manchester Warehouses), 1829 Jan 7. (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Vouchers (Richmond and Manchester Warehouses), 1829 Jan 24. (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Vouchers (Richmond and Manchester Warehouses), 1829 Apr 9. (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Vouchers (Richmond and Manchester Warehouses), 1829 Apr 17. (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - Vouchers (Richmond and Manchester Warehouses), 1829 June 5. (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - Vouchers (Richmond and Manchester Warehouses), 1829 June 25. (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - Vouchers (Richmond and Manchester Warehouses), 1829 Aug 13. (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - Vouchers (Richmond Warehouses), 1829 Oct 2. (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - Vouchers (Richmond and Manchester Warehouses), 1829 Nov 10. (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - Vouchers (Richmond and Manchester Warehouses), 1829 Nov 14. (Box 14, Folder 36)
  - Vouchers (Lynchburg Warehouses), 1829 Nov 17. (Box 14, Folder 37)
  - Vouchers (Richmond and Manchester Warehouses), 1830 Jan 6. (Box 14, Folder 38)
  - Vouchers (Fredericksburg Warehouses), 1830 Jan 8. (Box 14, Folder 39)
  - Vouchers (Richmond and Manchester Warehouses), 1830 Jan 26. (Box 14, Folder 40)
  - Vouchers (Johnson's Warehouse), 1830 Feb 13. (Box 14, Folder 41)
  - Vouchers (Richmond and Manchester Warehouses), 1830 Apr 8. (Box 14, Folder 42)
  - Vouchers (Petersburg Warehouses), 1830 Apr 27. (Box 14, Folder 43)
  - Vouchers (Richmond and Manchester Warehouses), 1830 May 24. (Box 14, Folder 44)
  - Vouchers (Richmond and Manchester Warehouses), 1830 June 11. (Box 14, Folder 45)
  - Vouchers (Richmond and Manchester Warehouses), 1830 July 7. (Box 14, Folder 46)
  - Vouchers (Richmond and Manchester Warehouses), 1830 Aug 14. (Box 14, Folder 47)
  - Vouchers (Richmond and Manchester Warehouses), 1830 Oct 19. (Box 14, Folder 48)
  - Vouchers (Richmond and Manchester Warehouses), 1830 Oct 28. (Box 14, Folder 49)
  - Vouchers (Tye River Warehouse), 1830 Oct 30. (Box 14, Folder 50)
  - Vouchers (Richmond and Manchester Warehouses), 1830 Nov 3. (Box 14, Folder 51)
  - Vouchers (Petersburg Warehouses), 1830 Nov 5. (Box 14, Folder 52)
  - Vouchers (Richmond and Manchester Warehouses), 1830 Nov 13. (Box 14, Folder 53)
  - Vouchers (Richmond and Manchester Warehouses), 1831 Jan 4. (Box 14, Folder 54)
  - Vouchers (Richmond and Manchester Warehouses), 1831 Jan 21. (Box 14, Folder 55)
  - Vouchers (Richmond and Manchester Warehouses), 1831 Feb 14. (Box 14, Folder 56)
  - Vouchers (Richmond and Manchester Warehouses), 1831 May 6. (Box 14, Folder 57)
  - Vouchers (Richmond and Manchester Warehouses), 1831 May 20. (Box 14, Folder 58)
  - Vouchers (Byrd's Warehouse), 1831 June 8. (Box 14, Folder 59)
  - Vouchers (Byrd's Warehouse), 1831 June 10. (Box 14, Folder 60)
  - Vouchers (Richmond and Manchester Warehouses), 1831 July 19. (Box 14, Folder 61)
  - Vouchers (Richmond and Manchester Warehouses), 1831 Aug 12. (Box 14, Folder 62)
  - Vouchers (Richmond and Manchester Warehouses), 1831 Sept 7. (Box 14, Folder 63)
  - Vouchers (Richmond and Manchester Warehouses), 1831 Sept 14. (Box 14, Folder 64)
  - Vouchers (Richmond and Manchester Warehouses), 1831 Oct 7. (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Vouchers (Lynchburg Warehouses), 1831 Oct 14. (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Vouchers (Petersburg Warehouses), 1831 Oct 29. (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Vouchers (Richmond and Manchester Warehouses), 1831 Nov 18. (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Vouchers (Norfolk Warehouses), 1831 Nov 21. (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Vouchers (Byrd's Warehouse), 1831 Dec 29. (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Vouchers (Richmond and Manchester Warehouses), 1832 Jan 14. (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Vouchers (Richmond and Manchester Warehouses), 1832 Feb 8. (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Vouchers (Richmond and Manchester Warehouses), 1832 Mar 15. (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Vouchers (Richmond and Manchester Warehouses), 1832 Mar 16. (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Vouchers (Fredericksburg Warehouses), 1832 Mar 22. (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Vouchers (Richmond and Manchester Warehouses), 1832 May 16. (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Vouchers (Richmond and Manchester Warehouses), 1832 May 18. (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Vouchers (Danville and Norfolk Warehouses), 1832 June 25. (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Vouchers (Scottsville Warehouse), 1832 July 12. (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Vouchers (Richmond and Manchester Warehouses), 1832 Aug 9. (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Vouchers (Richmond and Manchester Warehouses), 1832 Aug 17. (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Vouchers (Richmond and Manchester Warehouses), 1832 oct 3. (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Vouchers (Lynchburg Warehouses), 1832 Oct 12. (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Vouchers (Richmond and Manchester Warehouses), 1832 Oct 15. (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Vouchers (Petersburg Warehouses), 1832 Oct 20. (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Vouchers (Petersburg Warehouses), 1832 Oct 23. (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Vouchers (Tye River Warehouse), 1832 Oct 31. (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Vouchers (Petersburg Warehouses), 1832 Nov 16. (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Vouchers (Norfolk Warehouses), 1832 Dec 12. (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Vouchers (Richmond and Manchester Warehouses), 1833 Jan 11. (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Vouchers (Richmond and Manchester Warehouses), 1833 Jan 16. (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Vouchers (Byrd's Warehouse), 1833 Mar 20. (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Vouchers (Richmond and Manchester Warehouses), 1833 Apr 5. (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Vouchers (Richmond and Manchester Warehouses), 1833 June 14. (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Vouchers (Seabrook's and Shockoe Warehouses), 1833 Aug 14. (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - Vouchers (Seabrook's and Shockoe Warehouses), 1833 Oct 8. (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - Vouchers (Lynchburg Warehouses), 1833 Oct 28. (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - Vouchers (Planter's Warehouse), 1833 Nov 4. (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - Vouchers (Petersburg Warehouses), 1833 Nov 7. (Box 15, Folder 35)
  - Vouchers (Seabrook's Warehouse), 1833 Nov 15. (Box 15, Folder 36)
  - Vouchers (Petersburg Warehouses), 1833 Nov 25. (Box 15, Folder 37)
  - Vouchers (Richmond Warehouses), 1834 Jan 8. (Box 15, Folder 38)
  - Vouchers (Shockoe Warehouse), 1834 Mar 14. (Box 15, Folder 39)
  - Vouchers (Richmond Warehouses), 1834 June 13. (Box 15, Folder 40)
  - Vouchers (Richmond Warehouses), 1834 Aug 16. (Box 15, Folder 41)
  - Vouchers (Richmond Warehouses), 1834 Oct 9. (Box 15, Folder 42)
  - Vouchers (Unknown Warehouse), 1834 Oct 10. (Box 15, Folder 43)
  - Vouchers (Lynchburg Warehouses), 1834 Oct 17. (Box 15, Folder 44)
  - Vouchers (Richmond Warehouses), 1834 Oct 20. (Box 15, Folder 45)
  - Vouchers (Danville Warehouses), 1834 Nov 25. (Box 15, Folder 46)
  - Vouchers (Petersburg Warehouses), 1834 Nov 27. (Box 15, Folder 47)
  - Vouchers (Petersburg Warehouses), 1835 Jan 27. (Box 15, Folder 48)
  - Vouchers (Friend's and Planter's Warehouses), 1835 Feb 5. (Box 15, Folder 49)
  - Vouchers (Lynchburg Warehouses), 1835 Mar 9. (Box 15, Folder 50)
  - Vouchers (richmond and Manchester Warehouses), 1835 Apr 10. (Box 15, Folder 51)
  - Vouchers (Lynchburg Warehouses), 1835 May 8. (Box 15, Folder 52)
  - Vouchers (Richmond Warehouses), 1835 June 12. (Box 15, Folder 53)
  - Vouchers (Richmond Warehouses), 1835 Aug 15. (Box 15, Folder 54)
  - Vouchers (West Hill Warehouse), 1835 Aug 26. (Box 15, Folder 55)
  - Vouchers (Richmond Warehouses), 1835 Oct 8. (Box 15, Folder 56)
  - Vouchers (Richmond Warehouses), 1835 Nov 4. (Box 15, Folder 57)
  - Vouchers (Lynchburg Warehouses), 1835 Nov 27. (Box 15, Folder 58)